REJ AVERION

TEST ENGINEER

+49 176 31562519 | averionrej@gmail.com | Dortmund, Germany | linkedin.com/in/rejaverion

OVERVIEW

Test Engineer with 5+ years experience, developed post-silicon solutions and has affinity for software development, **seeking test engineering**, **product engineering**, **design verification**, **or similar roles** where I can leverage my test engineering background and manufacturing perspective to bring value to the company. Willing to relocate within Germany.

SKILLS

- Proficient ATE user: SPEA DOT400, LTX MX, ETS88, Teradyne uFLEX, Advantest T2000
- PCB Schematic Design
- Digital, Analog, High-speed, High-voltage electronics
- Test Development, DfT, BIST, ATPG
- Oscilloscope, VNA, AWG, DMM, HP3458A, other bench equipment; Soldering
- C++, Python, VBA, Visual Studio IDE
- Linux, Bash CLI and scripting
- JIRA, Git, SVN
- Gage R&R Study, Data Analysis, Statistics
- LTSpice, other simulation tools
- 8D Analysis, 3x5 Why analysis, Failure Mode Effect and Analysis
- Data Analysis, Statistics, CSV, XML, STDF files
- IC Manufacturing; Quality Assurance
- Effective use of Microsoft Excel / Google Sheets
- Microcontrollers, Arduino, Raspberry Pi
- SQL, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Java, MATLAB, Object-oriented programming
- Machine Learning
- Process optimization, product development
- Attention to detail
- Leadership, collaboration, effective communication
- Business acumen

EXPERIENCE

SilTest Semiconductors GmbH - Dortmund, Germany - 01.07.2023 – Present Test Engineer

- Lead a team of new engineers in debugging and qualifying probecards, DUT boards, adapterboards on Advantest T2000, LTX MX, and SZ Piranha platforms.
- Did manual repair and soldering of test hardware when necessary.

Manila Finest Technical Services - Dubai, United Arab Emirates - 18.02.2023 – 30.06.2023 Project Engineer

- Developed document generation webtool that streamlined creation of invoices, quotations, statement of account, payroll, and other documents
- Developed company website
- Coordinated materials procurement and project execution. Did on-site supervision to ensure quality of work and safety of personnel
- Designed 2D and 3D proposals in AutoCAD and Photoshop

Analog Devices, Inc. - Cavite, Philippines - 01.02.2018 – 17.02.2023 Senior Engineer, Test Development

- Designed, characterized, debugged high-bandwidth PCB's that meet GMSL, oLDI LVDS, MIPI, EDP, HDMI signal integrity and power integrity requirements.
- Developed fast and efficient ATE programs without compromising test coverage.
- Collaborated with international cross-functional teams on high-visibility projects with aggressive cycle times.
- Travelled to offshore sites for various engineering/manufacturing purposes.
- Developed/optimized test solutions for automotive serial link and battery management ICs on various automatic test equipment (ATE) platforms.
- Migrated high-volume products from constrained platforms/equipment into more cost-effective solutions, resulting in roughly 50 million USD in cumulative capex avoidance, 180% increase in throughput per product on average over the past 5 years.
- Wrote Python scripts and tools to automate various development tasks.
- Developed and facilitated ATE trainings for other test engineers.
- All other tasks associated with IC test development

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

- Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering
 - Emilio Aguinaldo College Cavite, Philippines 2012-2017
 - Top of the class GPA = 3.70/4.00
 - Best Final Year Project awardee Intoxication Detection based on Thermal Imaging and Machine Learning
 - Full scholarship awardee and Dean's Lister, 2012-2017
- Licensed Electronics Engineer 99th percentile scorer in nationwide Licensure Exam -2017
- Mechatronics Servicing National Certificate II from Philippines Technical Education and Skills Development Authority – 2016
- Data Analysis with Python freeCodeCamp March 2023

BIO

- Legal name: Thomas Randall Rejs Averion
- Birthplace: Metro Manila, Philippines
- Nationality: Filipino
- Gender: Male
- Current place of residence: Dubai, UAE
- Civil Status: Married
- Birthdate: 31 May 1996